上集回顾
Previously on "Lost"...
就是这儿 这有个界线
Right here, there's a line.
你要是越过着界线
You cross that line,
那就不是什么误会的事了
we go from misunderstanding to...something else.
我该怎么做?
What do I do?
去按那些按钮
That button has to be pushed.
我从来都没有输入过那些数字
I never entered the numbers.
我从来没碰过那些按钮
I never pressed the button.
你说谎
You're lying.
没有 我从不说谎
No, I'm done lying.
的确是降落伞
It's a parachute.
这样 bernard 谷类食品放在左边
All right.Cereal goes on the left, Bernard.
这样做会让你很麻烦吗?
So this isn't bothering you at all?
哪里的话
What's "this"?
好的 就是这个
Well, this.
这个
This.
为什么这么一包土豆条却让我感到困惑?
Why is a bag of potato chips gonna bother me?
难道你对这些东西是从哪儿来的就不感到一点好奇?
Well, aren't you remotely curiousas to where all this came from?
你就像刚从超市回来一样
You're acting like we just got back from the supermarket.
好的 我猜想我从来没有因为我所受到的恩惠而被质疑过
Well, I guess I was raised never to question my blessings.
我却对这些贴上古怪标签的食物感到奇怪
I was raised to question piles of food with weird labels
rose 这简直就是天上掉下来的馅饼
that just fall out of the sky, Rose.
亲爱的 只是因为天气不好吗?
Well, honey,just because you're having a bad day,
但也不用扯着嗓子喊啊
doesn't mean you have to raise your voice.
天气不好?我在这个岛的另外一边过了7个星期的糟糕日子,
Bad day? I've had seven weeks of bad days on the other side of the island,
只是努力活着 从而回到你的身边
just trying to stay alive so I could get back to you.
但是这却...
But here...
天哪 Rose 他们在沙滩上建了个厨房
my god, Rose,they've built a kitchen on the beach.
他们已经放弃了
They've given up.
放弃?放弃什么?
Given up? On what?
放弃离开这
On getting rescued.
你要处理下那个玩意儿吗?
You gonna get that?
你最后一次进去见他是什么时候
When's the last time you went in to see him?
几个小时前 他正在睡觉
Couple hours ago. He was sleeping.
-他吃了吗  -没有
-Did he eat  -Nope.
到现在已经两天了
That's two days now.
不吃不喝  什么都不说
No food. No water. Nothing to say.
我不知道你是怎么想的  我是等的不耐烦了
I don't know about you, but I'm tired of waiting.
我听说你没有什么胃口
I hear you've lost your appetite.
好样的 不说拉倒
OK. Don't talk.
我向来对和病人沟通就不擅长
I was never that good at bedside manner, anyway.
让我来给你肩膀的伤口换个药
I'm gonna change your dressing.
如果你想打什么主意的话 那你就有大麻烦了 所以 henry
If you try anything, we've got a problem. So, Henry...
Henry.
我正在想在我们调查清楚出 你到底是谁之前说些什么
I was thinking about something you were saying before we found out who you are.
这有点痛
This is gonna sting.
你一直说如果你是他们的其中一员的话
Yeah, you were saying that if you were one of them,
你就会把我们带进陷阱
that you'd lead us into a trap.
绑架我们的人 和我们做交易 用你做交易
Capture our people, force a trade. Us for you.
Henry 这真是个好主意
Pretty good idea, Henry.
既然你是他们中的其中一员 我想你现在最好充分利用时间
And since you are one of them, I thought now might be a good time to use it.
我打算越过那条不应该被越过的界线
I'm going out to the line that we're not supposed to cross
告诉他们你在我们手上
and telling them that we've got you.
如果他们想带你回去 那就得拿东西来换
And if they want you back, it's gonna cost 'em.
当我们把Walt换回来
And when we get Walt back...
那你惹的这些麻烦也算值了
you might just have been worth all the trouble.
Did you say something?
他们不会把walt还给你们的
They'll never give you Walt.
声明: 本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
欢迎访问官方论坛  www.YYeTs.net 在线观看 剧情讨论 学习交流
=====本字幕由以下成员荣誉制作 感谢他们的无私奉献======
翻译：Singa校对： BillSky
后期：xyz 双语制作：DrunkBat
========== 字幕总监制：七色九天 ==========
别踩油门 要不只会越陷越深
Don't gun it. You're digging yourself in.
-油门一点一点加  -恕我直言
-Just tap the gas, lightly.  -All due respect,
我都在雪地里开了一辈子车了 你介意我往后退一点吗
I have driven in snow my whole life. Mind stepping back?
你介意我往后退一点吗 你这样做不能
You have to rock it out. You're not gonna be able to...
-我打"AAA"吧  -为什么 难到这样他们就会送一个拖车过来
-I'm calling triple A.  -What, so they can send a tow truck?
相信我 我能搞定这一切
Trust me, I can do this.
好的 慢慢往上加一点油门
OK. Ease on the gas.
就是这样 你做得真棒
That's it. You're doing great!
差不多了
Almost!
继续 继续 继续  啊
Go, go, go!
你 你还好吗?
Are you OK?
是的 我很好
Oh, yeah. Sure, I'm fine.
你知道的 我几乎快要把它弄出来了
you know I would have gotten it out eventually.
当然 7月份马上就要到了
sure. July's right around the corner.
是的 感谢你帮助我
Well, thanks for helping me.
不客气
Sure.
顺便说一句 我叫rose
By the way, I'm Rose.
-我叫bernard  -对
-Oh...Bernard.  -Yeah.
-好的  -好的 好
-OK.  -Oh, OK. Yeah. OK.
-小心驾驶  -当然 你也小心
-Drive Drive safe, now, OK  -Yeah, yeah. You too.
-嗯  Bernard  -怎么了
-Um... Uh, Bernard?  -Yeah?
我能请你喝一杯咖啡吗
Can I buy you a cup of coffee?
啊 咖啡不错
Coffee would be nice.
是的 就这么说
Yeah. OK.
这可是我和其他人抢了半天才得到的 特意为你留的
I had to beat back half the group to get these. I saved them for you.
这不行  我在减肥
No way. I'm on a new diet.
只吃鱼 只喝水
Nothing but fish and water and...
鱼和水
fish and water.
Hurley 你在做什么
Hurley, what are you doing right now?
-和你妻子说话  -好的
-Talking to your wife.  -Good.
你能找到libby  5分钟后和她到那边的树那边见我吗
Can you and Libby meet me at the tree line in five minutes?
去叫一下Jin和Sun 还有Jenkins和那个做冷冻酸奶的家伙
And can you get Jin and Sun, Jenkins, and that frogurt guy?
-那个做冷冻酸奶的家伙?  -Neil
-The guy who made frozen yogurt?  -Neil
是的  还有craig以及你能找到的任何人
Yeah. And Craig, and anybody else you can get.
Bernard  你要干吗
Bernard? What are you up to?
我有个主意
I got an idea.
Richard  Craig  Ralph 到这来 我有一个好主意
Hey, Richard, Craig, Jerome, come here. I got a great idea...
我还是不确定他们到底愿不愿意换人
I'm not sure trading people's their thing.
与他谈话也没有什么用
talking to him is getting us nowhere.
所以 也许我们能给他想要的东西
So, maybe we can get something for him.
你要我和你一起去吗?
You want me to come with you?
所以 也许我们能给他想要的东西
You need to stay here.
你只要待在这就好
You need it more than I do.
哥们 听我的
Do yourself a favor, man.
-别单独去那  -好的
-Don't go out there alone.  -All right.
哈哈 原来是这样的
Ha-ha! That's how it's done.
正看着你呢
well, look at you.
那好像是 半个小时里的第四个吧
What, that's like four in the last half hour?
让我去叫吉尼斯纪录吧
Let me call the Guinness book.
你到底帮不帮我   我还要用我的时间多做些事呢
You want help or not? 'Cause I've got better things to do with my time.
快乐的一天 我们的微笑医生过来了
happy day. Here comes Dr. Giggles.
嗨  一个人啊
Hey, yourself.
我要再回到丛林里找 那个长胡子的"老朋友"谈谈
I'm going back to the jungle to talk to our friend with the beard.
看看我们能不能和他做个交易
See if we can make a trade.
俘虏交换
the old prisoner exchange.
难道你要叫上我一起去  顺便拿到那些枪
You're inviting me along 'cause you want a gun?
我不是在邀请你  我是在邀请kate
I'm not inviting you, I'm inviting Kate.
我已经有一把抢了,不过谢谢帮助.
And I've already got a gun, but thanks for offering.
你他妈的是怎么弄到枪的
How in the hell did you get a gun?
这有意义吗
Does it matter?
我收拾下我的东西
I'll get my things.
好的 我们已经被困在这岛上两个月了吧
OK, two months we've been on this island. Two months.
现在我们已经有了储水罐
And already we have a water trough,
也有了食物仓库
and we've got a food pantry,
所有人都能在那舱里洗澡
and people are taking showers in your hatch.
难道你们已经忘了我们 是落难到这岛上的吗
Have you forgotten that we all crashed on this island?
-现在好像没有人想回家  -你说什么  我们都想回家
-It's like none of you want to go home.  -How can you say that? Of course we do.
-那为什么我们不为此做点什么  -哥们 我们做过一个木筏
-Why aren't we doing anything about it?  -Dude, we like built a raft.
不过散架了
But, it got blown up.
好的 那么我们现在干吗
OK. So, what are we doing now?
那降落伞里面有那么多食物
That pallet of food had a parachute,
which means a plane dropped it here,
那也就意味着会有别的飞机经过这里
which means there are other planes that fly over the island.
所以我们要建造一个标志物 一个在沙滩上巨大的标志物
So, we are gonna build a sign, a massive sign along the beach.
那样的话 如果有飞机飞过这里 或者卫星拍照的时候
So, that way, if a plane flies over or a satellite takes pictures from up there
我们必须有十足的把握  别人知道我们在这该死的岛上
we wanna make damn sure that they know we're here,
让他们知道我们的存在
that they know about us.
也许我们应当先和jack说一下
Maybe we should speak to Jack about this first.
难道我们做什么事都要经过jack批准吗
do we have to run everything by Jack?
我的意思是他并不是我们的总统 他-他只是个医生
I mean, he's not the president. He's... He's a doctor.
而你只是个牙医
You're a dentist.
我能和你说上几分钟吗
Could I speak to you for just a second?
过来
Come here.
亲爱的 这支是个标志物 我看不出有什么不妥
Honey, it is just a sign. I don't see what the harm is.
问题是你说的那些飞机以及
The harm is you are telling these people about airplanes and satellites
不知从哪里冒出来的卫星
coming out of nowhere to save the day.
不知从哪里冒出来的卫星 我想回到属于我的生活中去
I'm just trying to do something. I want to get back to our life.
好样的 唯一不妥的就是 你正在给这里的人们一个错误的希望
Well, the only thing you are doing is giving these people false hope.
对不起
Excuse me.
我自己去造
I have a sign to build.
就这样吧 我希望马上就能开工
All right, I want to get this going right away.
我们已经等的太久了
We've waited long enough.
这简直太棒了 不是吗
It's just amazing, isn't it?
当然 它太漂亮了
sure, it's beautiful.
-感觉你有点心不在焉  -是的
-You're not impressed  -yeah.
那么 上帝要怎么做才能吸引你的注意呢
So, what does God have to do to get your attention?
Bernard  你在想什么
Bernard? What are you doing?
Rose...
我打了56年光棍了
I'd been a bachelor for 56 years.
直到我遇见你
And then I met you and we just fell into this rhythm,
就像...我们相遇就像上天安排好了似的
like we had known each other forever.
我总是梦想能找到像你这么好的人
I had always dreamed of finding somebody like you,
但是我不能再错过这样的机会
but I'd given up hope that I ever would.
-Bernard  -我知道 我知道 这太疯狂了
-Bernard...  -I know, I know. It's crazy.
我们才认识五个月
I mean, we just met five months ago.
但是五个月已经足够得久了
But five months is long enough
因为我知道哪怕只有五分钟 我也会这么想
because I knew after five minutes.
Rose...
我爱你
I love you.
你愿意嫁给我吗
Will you marry me?
Bernard  我快要死了
Bernard, I'm dying.
我病的很重 快要死了
I'm sick, and I'm dying.
能让我们单独呆一会儿吗
Would you excuse us for a minute, please?
前几年我的病情一度好转了
I've been in remission for the last couple of years,
但是现在 它不仅回来了反而又加重了
but now it's back, and this time it's not going away.
我的医生告诉我 我只有一年时间
My doctor says I have about a year...
也许还能再长一点
maybe a little longer.
你还没有回答我的问题
You haven't answered my question.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
Oh, I'm sure.
我愿意
Yes.
怎么 你和我一起待了48天 现在你却不和我讲话
Well, you bunk with a guy for 48 days, now he doesn't call or write.
你好  Bernard
Hello, Bernard.
-你们两个在干什么  -工作
-What have you boys got going up here  -Just working.
这样 听好了 我组织了一群人 要在海滩上建一个巨大的标志物
I got a team of folks throwing together a big sign down along the beach.
希望能有飞机或是卫星发现我们
Hopefully it'll get us spotted by a plane or satellite.
我们确信我们要有足够的人手来帮忙
We could use all the bodies we can get to help put it together.
对不起 我很忙
Sorry, I'm busy.
-Charlie  -对不起 Bernard
-Charlie  -Regrets, Bernard,
我只有两只手  但还是祝你好运
I've only got two hands, you know? Good luck, though.
好的 至少能给我几根大木头吗
Could I at least grab some of these logs?
-我们要用  -我们正在用它们
-We could sure use...  -We're using them.
-到底用来干嘛  -一座教堂
-For what, exactly  -A church.
-一座教堂  -是的
-A church  -Yes.
岛上的每一个人都在建些东西
Everybody on this island is building something.
我只是想让我们获救
I'm trying to get us saved.
bernard 每个人都有各自的方法
People are saved in different ways, Bernard.
我想我还是更喜欢 那个用木棒打自己同伴的你
I think I liked you better when you just hit people with your stick.
我还是喜欢现在的你
I like you just the way you are.
我要和他说话
I need to talk to him.
枪给jack了 门不能开
The gun's with Jack. The door stays closed.
但是如果你坚持要 就去说吧
But if you wanna talk to him, talk to him.
Henry 你能听见我说话吗
Henry, can you hear me?
是我John  Henry.
It's John, Henry.
Henry 你输入过那些数字吗
Henry, did you enter the numbers?
你到底有没有按按钮啊
Did you push the button or not?
Henry! 我要知道 我要你回答我
Henry! I need to know! I want you to answer me!
回答我
Answer me!
henry你能听见我说话吗
Answer me, you hear me?
大家都怎么了?
What happened to everybody?
嗯 craig在哪儿  frogurt去哪儿了
Where's Craig? Where's Frogurt?
好吧 好吧 咱们继续 我们要把标志物弄满整个沙滩
OK, all right, moving on. We're gonna put this sign across this entire beach.
也就是说字母必须足够大  40英尺左右
Which means the letters have to be really big, about 40 feet.
这些黑石头要尽可能的与这些沙子区分开来
These black rocks will get maximum contrast with the sand.
伙计 我们好像要更多的石头
Dude, we're gonna need a lot more rocks.
是的 hurley我们的确要更多的石头
Yes, Hurley, we are gonna need a lot more rocks.
内岛大概半英里有一片石灰岩
There's a lava field about half a mile inland that's loaded with them.
我们要把它们搬过来 我们要分成两人一组
We'll haul them out in two-man teams.
所以你们两个一组
So, you guys double up,
我在沙滩上做字母的图形 我们开工吧
and I am gonna start sketching out the letters in the sand. Let's do this.
嗨 我可以做字母的图形
Hey, I can sketch the letters.
每一个人都有工作 hurley. 我做我的 你做你的
Everybody's got a job, Hurley. I do my job, you do yours.
什么 他在说什么
What? What did he say?
我想他对整个关于从半英里外的地方 运石头过来并不感到疯狂
I think he's not so crazy about the whole carry-the-rocks-a-half-mile thing.
好吧  嗯 这需要时间
OK. Look, this is gonna take time,
但是只有这样才能让我们离开这个地方 这不值得吗
but if this is the thing that gets us off this place, isn't that worth it?
你知道的 罗马也不是一天建成的
Rome wasn't built in a day, you know.
啊 不 你不知道...好了我们开始吧 加油干
No, you don't know. OK, all right, let's get started. Come on.
我们迷路了
We're lost.
甜心 这可不是你说迷路就迷路哦
You saying we're lost doesn't make us lost.
我知道我们在哪儿
I know exactly where we are.
我也是
Me, too.
我知道我们在澳洲内陆原地打转呢
Driving around in circles in the middle of the outback.
那就是为什么我想去海边度蜜月了
That's why I wanted to be on a beach for our honeymoon.
谢天谢地 文明世界
Thank goodness, civilization.
Bernard 我们去明确一下方向
Bernard, let's get directions.
哦 我不需要方向
Oh, I don't need directions.
我告诉过你 亲爱的 我们没有迷路
I told you, honey, we're not lost.
Bernard 怎么了
Bernard, what's going on?
我带你来这里 是因为我要你来见一个人
I brought you out here because I want you to see this man.
他叫 isaac of uluru  他已经帮助了成百上千的人
His name is Isaac of Uluru, and he's helped hundreds of people.
现在 我知道这看上去怎样  但是请相信我 他完全信得过
Now, I know how it looks but, believe me, he is completely legit.
Bernard 你带我来做信仰治疗
Bernard, you brought me to a faith healer?
他真的可以帮上忙 rose
He's the real deal, Rose.
曾经我告诉别人你的情况
Once I started telling people about your situation,
接到到三个不同的电话都向我推荐他
I got three calls recommending him.
我的情况
My "situation"?
这就是为什么要我来澳大利亚的原因
This is why you wanted to come to Australia?
-带我来看一个怪人  -不 他不是怪人
-To bring me to some kind of a kook?  -No, he's not.
Rose 我捐了 $10,000 只是为了带你来见他
I made a $10,000 donation just to get you in to see him.
-基本看来  -我不需要
-Normally...  -I didn't ask for this!
这只是
This is...
Bernard...
我可以平静得面对发生在我身上的一切
I have made my peace with what's happening to me.
但是我不能
I haven't.
rose 我不能什么也不做
I can't just do nothing, Rose.
这不是我 这不是真实的我
That's not me. That's not who I am.
我得去尝试
I have to try.
rose 你愿意尝试吗
Will you try, Rose?
为了我
For me.
好的 这很棒 这真是个巨大的标志物
It's gonna be great. A really big sign.
太棒了
That's great.
如果你有时间来修你的房子  你就有时间来搬那些石头
If you have time to fix your hut, you have time to move some rocks.
我们需要你的帮忙
Come on, we could really use your help.
你在联合他们建沙场遇到了麻烦 对吗
What? You got union trouble down at the sand factory, Norma Rae?
来吧 sawyer 我需要你的帮忙
Come on, Sawyer. I need your help.
你说呢  没门
Now, what do you say?
我说
I say... Pasadena.
-我希望你能开心  -关于什么
-Well, I hope you're happy.  -About what?
早上我还有15个人愿意一起造那个标志物 但是现在就只剩4个了
This morning I had 15 people willing to work on the sign. Now I'm down to four.
是我的过错吗
And how is that my fault?
至少我希望得到你的支持
At the very least, I expected your support.
但是你却公然反对我
You had to go and attack me.
你还停下来好好想过  那些人退出的原因
Have you ever stopped to think, maybe the reason people are quitting
是你的管理方法上出了问题
is because you've got yourself a management problem?
rose 你到底是怎么了
What is the matter with you, Rose?
我只是想试着做些什么
I am just trying to do something.
那就对了 你总是在尝试做着什么
That's right. You're always trying to do.
为什么你不能任其自然呢
Why can't you just let things be?
如果我没有努力尝试 你就不会在这
If I didn't always have to do something, you wouldn't be here.
我很荣幸
I'm flattered.
嗯? 为什么
Yeah? Why is that?
因为你选择我和你一起去而不是sawyer
Because you chose me to go with you instead of Sawyer.
我先问的sayid 但是  他拒绝了我
I asked Sayid first, but he turned me down.
我只有问你 因为 他们 不需要你
And I only asked you because they don't want you.
他们抓住你不放 用枪威胁你
They grabbed you, had you at gunpoint.
他们本可以抓走你 但却没有
They coulda kept you, but they didn't.
话说回来 他们也不需要我
Then again, they didn't really want me either.
损坏的货物  我们两个
Damaged goods... both of us.
那是什么
What's that?
Kate...
-是个玩具  -等等 等等 不
-It's a doll.  -Wait, don't!
别 别
Don't! Don't!
对不起
Sorry.
-你还好吗  -是的
-You OK?  -Yeah.
还好能听见我讲话
good, so you can hear me.
这不会是他们设置的一个陷阱吧
This isn't one of theirs.
不 这还不够老练
No, it's not sophisticated enough.
一定是rousseau做的其中一个陷阱 希望她离这不是很远
Must be one of Rousseau's traps. Hopefully she's not far from here.
也许她一个星期后才出现
Could be a week before she shows up.
-你在干什么  -我正试着那我的枪
-What are you doing?  -I'm trying to get the gun.
-我的手翻不过来  -好的 这 我来
-I can't get my arm around.  -All right, here, let me...
好的
All right.
对不起  我可不想对你开枪
Sorry, I don't want to shoot you.
好的
OK.
你拿到了吗
You got it?
-好的 准备好了吗  -是的
-OK, ready?  -Yeah.
拿到了 拿到了 拿到了
Got it! Got it, got it, got it!
-这 拿到了  -现在把枪给我
-Got it.  -All right. Now, give me the gun.
-为什么  -试着射那个结
-Why? What for?  -I'm gonna try to shoot the rope.
我的枪法比你准
I'm a better shot than you.
真的吗
Oh, really?
当然 我告诉过你  我从小和我父亲一起打猎
Yeah. I told you, I grew up hunting with my dad.
该死的
Damn it!
好样的 至少他们知道我们在哪里了 好的 现在把枪给我
at least they know where we are. OK, now, give me the gun.
-难道你还要再浪费一颗子弹吗  -别担心
-Are you gonna waste another bullet?  -Don't worry.
我们还有13颗可以互相射击的子弹 加油
We'll still have 13 more to shoot each other with. Come on.
好的  反正你的角度比我的好
Fine. You have a better angle than I anyway.
如果我射中了你就把这当作借口吧
that's gonna be your excuse when I make the shot?
如果你打中的话
When you make the shot.
好的
OK.
好枪法
Nice shot.
不!不!不!不!不!不!
No! No-no-no-no-no!
全做错了
You're doing it all wrong!
我告诉过你排成三行
I told you, three rows!
三行 那样你才可以从天上看见它
Three, so they can see it from the air!
三行 那又有多难
Three rows. How hard is that?
难道什么都要我自己做吗
Do I have to do everything myself?
不! 不!不!不! 不!jin 不!等等
No. No-no-no! No, Jin! No, wait.
求求你
Please.
我只是想带我妻子回家
I just want to get my wife home.
Rose.
我想带Rose回家
I want to get Rose home.
对不起
Sorry.
你在我的地盘上
You're in my spot.
我可以走
I can move.
-你可以吗  -噢 那很有趣
-Can you?  -Oh, that's funny.
我猜你的幽默感和你腿一起被困在门里面了
I guess your sense of humor got trapped under that door with your leg.
我看见你丈夫走进丛林了 搬石头
I saw your husband walking through the jungle, hauling rocks.
他正在在沙滩上建一个巨大的标志物 那样卫星可以看见它
He's building a big sign in the sand, so the satellites will see it.
他还不能区分什么是徒劳无功
That man doesn't know the difference between an errand and a fool's errand.
这样 rose 我们中绝大多数都不能
Well, Rose, most of us don't.
那么你来这下面干什么 john
So, what are you doing down here, John?
我都不记得上一次你走出舱门是什么时候的事
Can't remember the last time I saw you out of that hatch.
我受不了那个舱了
I'm done with the hatch.
你现在只是心情比较沮丧
now, you're just frustrated.
你很快就能丢掉那个夹板在岛上到处跑了
You'll be out of that splint and running around the island again in no time.
jack说这至少得用上4个星期
And yet, Jack said it'd be at least four weeks.
但是 亲爱的 你和我都知道 其实并没那么久
But, honey, you and I both know it's not gonna take that long.
这边走 Rose
Right this way, Rose.
你就是Rose
You must be Rose.
为什么不坐呢
Why don't you have a seat?
那么 要怎么做
So, how does this work?
我坐在这 你唱赞歌吗或者祈祷或是其他什么
I sit here and you chant or pray or what?
在地球上某个地方有着很巨大的能量
There are certain places with great energy,
就像现在我们所在的地方一样
spots on the Earth like the one we're above now.
可能是地质能量 磁能
Perhaps this energy is geological, magnetic...
或是其他什么
or perhaps it's something else.
在适当的时候
And, when possible,
我接收这些能量把它给别人
I harness this energy and give it to others.
我可以吗
May I?
什么
What...
怎么了
What... What is it?
对不起
I'm sorry.
我不能帮你 Rose
I can't do anything for you, Rose.
我本来也不指望
I didn't expect you to.
并不是说你不能被治愈
It's not that you can't be healed.
就像我说的  有不同的能量
Like I said...there's different energies.
对你而言 这不是正确的地方
This is not the right place for you.
哪里才是正确的地方
Where is the right place?
我希望我知道
I wish I knew.
-我将把你丈夫的募捐还给他  -不要这样
-I'll return your husband's donation...  -Don't.
我告诉他你治好了我
I'm gonna tell him you fixed me.
I'm going to tell him you fixed me.
你刚才说的是什么意思
What did you mean back there?
-什么  -在网子里
-What?  -In the net.
你说他们很老练
You said they were sophisticated, the Others.
上个星期小孩病了 Claire 和我走进丛林
Last week when the baby got sick, Claire and I went into the jungle,
却发现了另一个舱
and found another hatch.
-什么  -像一个医疗站
-What?  -Like a medical station.
没有你要用的东西 全部都清空了 但是
There was nothing you could use, it was all cleared out. But...
我发现了一些橱柜  它们里面都是些破的和脏的衣服
I found some lockers. They had clothes inside, all worn and dirty,
衣服都是挂着的  像就像演出的衣服 你知道吧
but they were on hangers, like costumes, you know?
还有化妆箱
And there was a makeup kit...
和假须
and a fake beard.
你打算什么时候告诉我这些
When were you gonna tell me this?
当你决定让我回到舱里的时候
When you decided to let me back in the club.
什么
What?
你可以把其中一个锁在舱里 一个星期 却什么都没说
You can keep one of them locked up in the hatch for a week and say nothing,
但那时 当我
but then when I...
我们到了
We're here.
你确定? 我
Are you sure? I...
那就是他们向sawyer射击的地方
That's where they took the shot at Sawyer.
在那里 那里就是他们把 套着包的你从草丛里推出来的地方
Over there is where they pushed you out of the jungle with a bag on your head.
这就是
And right there is where I...
我放下枪的地方
where I laid my guns down.
我回来了
Hey, I'm back!
你说你正监视着我们
You say you're watching us?
听见我的话了吗
You hear me?
我们手里有你们的人
We've got your man.
如果你要他回去 你们就快点出来
You want him back, you're gonna have to come out here.
快出来
Come on out!
-Jack  -我知道你们在那儿
-Jack!  -I know you're there!
-我知道你们能听见我讲话  -Jack 他们不在这
-I know you can hear me.  -Jack, they're not here.
我就在这里不走知道你出来和我对话
I'll be right here until you talk to me.
我就在这里
I'll be right here.
我给你带来了点晚餐
I brought you some supper.
谢谢 你只要把它放在那里就好
Thanks. You can just set it down there.
他们人呢
Where is everybody?
我欠你一个道歉
I owe you an apology.
你没有什么要和我道歉的 这只是我自己该死的错误 让我自己待在这里
You don't have anything to be sorry for. It's my fault I'm here by myself.
我不是为了那个向你道歉
That's not why I'm apologizing.
我对你说谎了
I lied to you.
在澳大利亚  Isaac  他没能治好我
Back in Australia... Isaac, he didn't heal me.
他什么也没做
He didn't do anything.
-他当然做了...你...  -Bernard  他没能治好我
-Of course he did. You're...  -Bernard, he didn't heal me.
但是这并不意味着我没有好
But that doesn't mean I'm not healed.
当你生病的时候
When you're sick
你可以感觉到原本在身上并没有的东西
and you have something inside you that doesn't belong there,
你可以感觉到它
you can feel it.
坠机之后 我在也感觉不到了
And after the crash... I couldn't feel it anymore.
起初 我以为我被撞晕了
At first I thought it was just shock...
但那不是
but it wasn't.
就是这个地方
It's this place.
但是--但是你说isaac治好了你
But you said Isaac fixed you.
我那样说
I told you that,
是不想让你 再浪费剩下来的时间 我们要留下来一起做一些事情
so that you wouldn't spend what time we had left trying to do something.
Rose 可能只是略微好了一点
Rose, you could just be in remission.
你怎么知道不是isaac治好了你
How do you know it wasn't Isaac who healed you?
-你怎么知道他没有治好你  -我知道
-How do you know he didn't heal you?  -I know.
我知道
I know.
是你的吗
These yours?
是的 谢谢
Thank you.
不客气
You're welcome.
相信我
Trust me.
我知道
I know.
你不想被救离这里 是不是
You don't want to be rescued, do you?
你是觉得如果你离开这 它又会回来
You think if you leave, it'll come back.
如果你不想离开
And if you can't leave...
我也不离开
neither can I.
我们永远也不离开这 Rose
We won't ever leave, Rose.
我愿意
I would...
我会把这些标记拆掉 但是  反正我们开始没多久
I would offer to take down the sign, but we didn't get very far.
是我按的按钮
I pressed your button.
按钮不是我的
It's not my button.
你去了哪里
Where did you go?
我只是需要 伸展一下我的双腿
I just needed to... stretch my legs.
jack 你还要等多久
How long are you gonna wait, Jack?
直到得到回音
Until I get my voice back.
我还会再喊几声
And then I'm gonna yell some more.
可能他们根本就没听见
Maybe they can't hear you.
他们一定听得见
They can hear me.
对不起 我吻了你
I'm sorry I kissed you.
没什么大不了的
I'm not.
Michael!
==============|  YYeTs字幕组招募启示  |==============
英文字幕录制(居住在加拿大和美国)  双语字幕校正   时间轴调整
英语翻译   欧美影视新闻翻译  影视评论  论坛版主  美工人员
服务器提供者  发布宣传  联系地址：www.YYeTs.com
==== YYeTs属于网络爱好者组织 加入者仅凭个人兴趣爱好 无报酬 ====